

Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application
Programming, Client Management, Web Development, Algorithm Development, Data
Analysis, System Analysis, Data Visualization, Machine
Learning, Python, JIRA, Panda, JIRA, GIT, Mongo DB



Current Designation: Software Engineer Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 2 Month(s)

Current Company: Atmecs Technologies Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Mechanical]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Client Management, Web Development, Algorithm Development, Data Analysis, System Analysis, Data Visualization, Machine

Learning, Python, JIRA, Panda, JIRA, GIT, Mongo DB

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Having around 5 years experienced in industry.and experienced in ML Engineer in building successful algorithms & predictive models. Highly interested at Image based work, and NLP, I love to spend time with web scraping, data analysis & visualisation. Passionate engineer & thriving analyst with the ability to apply ML techniques & algorithm development to solve real-world business problems.

Work Experience

Atmecs Technologies as Software Engineer

Mar 2018 to Till Date

- * Worked on and Machine Learning Projects and deep learning projects as well as python api dev using flask.
- * Created Pipelines, generic templets for automate process of machine learning steps.
- * Worked on Data cleaning and data preprocessing and EDA for different client data.

Cloudedz private limited as Software Engineer

Nov 2017 to Mar 2018

Worked on and Data Cleaning and processing Tasks.

* Worked on Python Automation scripting, web-scraping, model creation and creating proof of concept.

Smaap Technologies as Software Engineer

Aug 2015 to Sep 2017

Developed client side application for different industry like e-commerce, Booking apps, tracking apps

* Started working on Python Backend Development with frameworks like Flask.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Mechanical) from SOA UNIVERSITY in 2015

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Intermediate

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Python			
OPENCV			
Mongo Db			
Tensorflow, Keras			
Pandas, Numpy, Sklearn			
Jira, Review Board			
Git, Bitbucket, Scrum			
PAYMENT Gateway			
AWS, Google Cloud platform			
Java, Anaconda			
Scikit-Learn, NumPy, Seaborn			
NLTK, BeautifulSoup			
Matplotlib, Jupyter Notebook			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Oriya				

Affirmative Action

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization